Guide to the South Africa Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Original accession, 1990-1997
  - Independent Electoral Commission (IEC), 1994 March-Apr, undated (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - Independent Forum for Electoral Education (IFEE), 1993 Jun, undated (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - Inkatha Freedom Party (IFP), 1992 June-1993 Jan, undated (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - Institute for a Democratic Alternative for South Africa (IDASA), 1993 March- 1994 Apr, June, 1996 June (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - Institute for Multi-party Democracy (MPD)
    - 1992 (Box 24, Folder 312)
    - 1993 (Box 24, Folder 313)
    - 1994 (Box 24, Folder 314)
    - 1995, 1996, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 315)
  - Institute for the Study of Man in Africa, 1992 September (Box 24, Folder 316)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA), Hanover, New Hampshire, 1994 December-1995 June (Box 24, Folder 317)
  - International Conference of the Anti-Apartheid Movement on Southern Africa, London ["Southern Africa: Making Hope a Reality"], 1993 June 14-15 (Box 24, Folder 318)
  - International Defence and Aid Fund for Southern Africa (IDAF), 1992 May, undated (Box 24, Folder 319)
  - International Freedom Foundation [includes report "Codesa: New Realities and Old Contradictions"], 1992 (Box 24, Folder 320)
    See also: South Africa Collection, 1990-1997 (inclusive), 1992-1996 (bulk) Folder 281
  - International Socialist Organization (ISO) [Barnard/Columbia], undated (Box 24, Folder 321)
  - Irish Anti-Apartheid Movement [Dublin], 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 322)
  - The Islamic Party (IP), undated (Box 25, Folder 323)
  - "Johannesburg Municipal General Elections 26 Oct 1988 and By Elections to 23 June 1993" (Box 25, Folder 324)
  - Julaka: A Newsletter for Those Interested in South Africa, Maryland, 1997 Feb/March (Box 25, Folder 325)
  - The Keep It Straight and Simple Party (KISS), undated (Box 25, Folder 326)
  - Kwazulu/Natal [includes constitution], 1992 December 1, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 327)
  - Land Resource and Information Centre (LRIC), 1995 May/June (Box 25, Folder 328)
  - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights, Washington, D. C., 1992 July (Box 25, Folder 329)
  - The Liaison Group of National Anti-Apartheid Movements in the Countries of the European Community, 1993 February (Box 25, Folder 330)
  - Luso-South African Party (LUSAP), undated (Box 25, Folder 331)
  - Maoist International Movement (MIM), Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1993 May (Box 25, Folder 332)
  - Mass Workers' Party (MWP), undated (Box 25, Folder 333)
  - MAST [facilitators' guide], [1994?] (Box 25, Folder 334)
    See also: South Africa Collection, 1990-1997 (inclusive), 1992-1996 (bulk) Folder 309
  - Matla Trust (MT), undated
  - Media Monitoring Project (MMP), undated (Box 25, Folder 335)
  - Muslims [includes The Call of Islam ], 1993, 1994, undated (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - National Children's Rights Committee (NCRC), undated (Box 25, Folder 337)
  - National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1996 February 27 (Box 25, Folder 338)
  - National Inauguration Committee (NIC), 1994 May (Box 25, Folder 339)
  - National Land Committee (NLC), 1995 Feb, undated (Box 25, Folder 340)
    See also: South Africa Collection, 1990-1997 (inclusive), 1992-1996 (bulk) Folder 388
  - National Party (NP), 1992-1996, undated (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - "National Peace Accord" [supplement to the Financial Mail ], 1993 April (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - National Peace Campaign, 1993 September (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - National Union of Metal Workers of South Africa (NUMSA), 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 344)
  - National Union of Mineworkers (NUM), 1993 Apr/May (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Negotiation News, 1992 April-Dec, 1993 March-Dec, 1994 March-April (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - New Era Schools Trust (NEST), undated (Box 26, Folder 347)
  - New York African Studies Association (NYASA) Newsletter, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 348)
  - Non-Governmental Organizations (NGO), New York, 1994 August (Box 26, Folder 349)
  - Pan Africanist Congress (PAC) of Azania [South Africa], 1992-1994, undated (Box 26, Folder 350)
  - Project Vote/ Voter Education: Manual for Trainers, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 351)
  - Republiek Van Suid-Afrika [Republic of South Africa], Department of Education, 1994 Sep, 1995 March (Box 26, Folder 352)
  - The Soccer Party, [1994?] (Box 26, Folder 353)
  - Socialist Workers Organization, 1996 September (Box 26, Folder 354)
  - South African Broadcasting Corporation (SABC), 1992 July 13-26, 1993 January (Box 26, Folder 355)
  - South African Chamber of Business (SACOB), 1994 July (Box 26, Folder 356)
  - South African Clothing and Textile Workers Union (SACTWU), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 357)
  - South African Communication Service, undated (Box 26, Folder 358)
  - South African Communist Party (SACP)
    - General [newsletters, manifesto, discussion documents], 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 359)
    - Umsebenzi / The African Communist, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 360)
  - South African Institute of International Affairs, 1992, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 361)
  - South African Institute of Race Relations (SAIRR)
    - General [press releases, topic papers, speeches, member services, miscellaneous], 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 362)
    - Fast Facts
      - 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 363)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 364)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 365)
    - Frontiers of Freedom, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 366)
    - Spotlight, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 367)
    - Watchdog, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 368)
  - South African Medical and Dental Practitioners (SAMDP), 1993 August 14-15, December (Box 27, Folder 369)
  - South African Municipal Workers Union (SAMWU), undated (Box 27, Folder 370)
  - South African National Council for the Aged, undated (Box 27, Folder 371)
  - South African Observer, 1992 May (Box 27, Folder 372)
  - South African Patriot and South African Patriot in Exile, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 373)
  - South African Police, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - The South African Political Research Association (SAPRA), 1992 January-October (Box 27, Folder 375)
  - South African Prisoners Organization for Human Rights (SAPOHR), 1992 (Box 27, Folder 376)
  - South African Students' Congress (SASCO), 1992 June (Box 27, Folder 377)
  - South African Students' Press Union (SASPU), 1993 February-May, 1994 February, undated (Box 27, Folder 378)
  - South Africa Exclusive [political/economic issues], 1993 Jul/August (Box 27, Folder 379)
  - Southern Africa Postcard Research Group (SAPRG), 1992 September (Box 27, Folder 380)
  - Southern Africa Review, 1992 February-Nov, 1993 December (Box 27, Folder 381)
  - Southern Africa Transport and Communications Commission (SATCC), New York, 1993 January-March (Box 27, Folder 382)
  - Southern African Training Program of the African-American Institute, 1992 January (Box 27, Folder 383)
  - SouthScan, London [monthly regional bulletin], 1992 Oct, 1993 May (Box 27, Folder 384)
  - Transitional Executive Council (TEC), 1994, undated (Box 27, Folder 385)
  - The TranLis Coalition [Transforming Our Library and Information Services], McLean, Virginia, undated (Box 27, Folder 386)
  - Transvaal Indian Congress (TIC), 1994 February (Box 27, Folder 387)
  - Transvaal Rural Action Committee (TRAC), 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 388)
  - United Nations
    - Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Discrimination Against Women (CEDAW), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 389)
    - Human Rights Day, 1993 December 10 (Box 28, Folder 390)
    - Press releases, undated (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - United States Agency for International Development [voter education project], 1993 (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - United States Conference of Mayors, 1995 January (Box 28, Folder 393)
  - United States 102d Congress [S. Res. 301], 1992 May (Box 28, Folder 394)
  - United States Institute of Peace, 1993 September (Box 28, Folder 395)
  - University of Bophuthatswana, 1992 September (Box 28, Folder 396)
  - University of Cape Town, 1992, undated (Box 28, Folder 397)
  - University of Illinois, 1993 February (Box 28, Folder 398)
  - University of Natal, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 399)
  - University of South Africa, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 400)
  - University of the Western Cape, 1992 January-May, 1993 October (Box 28, Folder 401)
  - University of Witwatersrand, 1993 April-Sep, undated (Box 28, Folder 402)
  - University of Zululand, 1993 September (Box 28, Folder 403)
  - The Washington Office on Africa, 1993-1994, undated (Box 28, Folder 404)
  - Western Cape Province, Ministry of Health and Social Services, undated (Box 28, Folder 405)
  - Winning Minds Management Consultants [voter education], 1993, undated (Box 28, Folder 406)
  - Women's Rights Peace Party (WRPP), [1994?] (Box 28, Folder 407)
  - Workers International to Rebuild the Fourth International (WI), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 408)
  - Workers' List Party, 1994 Apr, undated (Box 28, Folder 409)
  - Workers Organization for Socialist Action (WOSA), 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 410)
  - Workers' Solidarity, 1995 May-Jun, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 411)
  - Ximoko Progressive Party (XPP), undated (Box 28, Folder 412)
  - Yale University, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 413)
  - Young South Africans for a Christian Civilization, 1992 Jan/March (Box 28, Folder 414)
  - Subject files
    - Art, culture, and entertainment, 1993-1996, undated (Box 29, Folder 415)
    - Business/Investments, 1992, 1994, undated (Box 29, Folder 416)
    - Diamond Industry/DeBeers, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 417)
    - Elections
      - [memorabilia consisting of bumper stickers, buttons, key rings, scarves, ties, and miscellaneous items] (Box 30, Folder 418 - 422)
      - [memorabilia consisting of tee shirts, hats and puzzles] (Box 31)
  - Foreign relations, [1990?], 1996 (Box 32, Folder 423)
  - Magazines [various titles, random issues]
    - 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 424)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 425)
  - Newspapers [various titles, random issues]
    - 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 426)
    - 1994 Mar-Aug (Box 32, Folder 427)
    - 1995 (Box 32, Folder 428)
    - 1996 (Box 32, Folder 429)
  - Voter education, 1993-1995, undated (Box 32, Folder 430)
- Additional Material, Accession 1999-M-057
  Scope and Contents
  This accession consists of printed material and memorabilia relating to the bid put forth by the city of Cape Town to the International Olympic Committee to host the summer games of the XXVIII Olympiad in the year 2004.
  - Printed material, 1994-1996
    - General information [includes finances, housing, publicity, security, sports facilities, transportation, and related topics] (Box 1, Folder 1 - 5)
    - "Strategic Environmental Assessment" (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Investment opportunities (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "2004" [official magazine of the Cape Town 2004 Bid], 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Memorabilia
    - Button badges and flag (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Clothing [necktie, scarf] (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Stationery, decals (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Wall hanging/banner (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Audiovisual
    - "Olympic Bid- 'One World'" [videotape] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Oversize
    - Calendars, posters (Box 3)
- Additional Material, Accession 2000-M-046
  This accession contains additional printed materials arranged alphabetically by organization name, personal name, or title of publication.
  - "About Friends: The Friends for Life Newsletter", 1996 November (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Affirmative Action in the Public Sphere" [draft, Department of Public Service and Administration], 1998 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Africa Confidential, vol. 34, no. 18, 1993 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Africa Fund [memo titled, "Working for Africa's Future"], 1997 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - African National Congress (ANC)
    - ANC election press centre information and safety handbook, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ANC January 8 statements
      - "1998: Popular mobilization for the consolidation of peoples' power", 1998 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - "1999: Year of Mass Mobilization for the Renewal of the Democratic Mandate", 1999 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ANC Youth League (ANCYL)
      - Horizon [Journal of the ANCYL], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - June 16 Youth Day [International booklet of ANCYL, no. 1], 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 19th National Congress of ANCYL [held at Durban Exhibition Centre], 1996 February 29-March 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Help us build South Africa's economy: the ANC and the business sector, working together for a prosperous future", undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Memorial service for the late Godfrey Mokgomane Pitje" [former chairman of the ANC Youth League, includes obituary clippings from Sowetan ], 1997 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "The Masakhane Campaign" [a manual for the ANC, Allience and MDM], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "Policing in the New South Africa" [a discussion paper], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "The State and Social Transformation" [discussion document], 1996 November (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "Strategies and Tactics" [booklet outlining ANC's strategies and tactics as amended at its 50th National Conference], 1997 December (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Truth and Reconciliation Commission (TRC)
      - "Appendices to the Second Submission by ANC", 1997 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - "Further Submissions and Reponses by the ANC to Questions Raised by the Truth and Reconciliation Commission", 1997 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - "Nothing but the truth...," Mangosuthu Buthelezi [open letter published in the Johannesburg Star ], 1997 August 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - "The Pan Africanist Congress of Azania: a Viable Alternative? or a Flat Spare Tyre?" [ANC's reflection on the origins, track-record, present performance and policies of PAC), undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - "Walter Sisulu is 80 years old on 18th May 1992" [press release] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albany Museum
    - "Education at the Albany Museum" [pamphlet], 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "The Elephant's Child" [Albany Museum newsletter, vol. 18, no. 3], 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Anglogold: a Gold Company for the 21st Century", 1998 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Association of Concerned Africa Scholars, "The Case Against DOD and CIA Involvement in Funding the Study of Africa" [public statement], undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Big Issue, nos. 2, 3, and vol. 2, no. 8 [International Network of Street Papers], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Canon Collins Educational Trust for Southern Africa [memos to friends and supporters], 1995 Jun, Dec, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cantilevers, first quarter, vol. 3 [a five-issue international peace and conflict resolution publication series], 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cape Town
    - The Last Days of District Six [photographs by Jan Greshoff], undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "Sam Ramsamy: S. A.'s 'Mr. Olympics'" [concerning the Cape Town bid to host the 2004 Olympics], undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "CTPA News" [a publication of Cape Town Teachers' Professional Association, vol. 4, no. 2], 1994 June (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Carapace, nos. 3, 6, and 16 [a poetry magazine], undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CASE (Community Agency for Social Equity)
    - "'Finishing the Job?' Deepening democracy and delivering benefits through successful local government elections" [research and analysis for Project Vote], undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "Surviving the Transition: Alternative Media and Reading Culture in the New South Africa" [an overview of selected publications associated with the Independent Magazine Group, researched and written by Jean de Castro, David Everatt and Mark Orkin], undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Caversham Press and Educational Trust [information bulletin], undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Centre for Education Policy Development
    - "Briefing Notes on the National Colloquium on Local/District Governance in Education", 1995 June 28-29 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - "Known Practices, Unknown Theory: Bursaries and Loans in Contemporary South African Tertiary Education," by Charles van Onselen [address to recipients and trustees of the E. Oppenheimer Memorial Trust], 1996 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Centre for Policy Studies, "Co-operative Governance and North West Province" [proceedings of a workshop held in the chamber of the Mafikeng (Mafeking) Town Council], 1997 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Confronting Africa's Weaknesses," Yoweri Kaguta Museveni [address to the 7th Pan African Congress held in Kampala, Uganda], 1994 April 4-8 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Constitution Assembly, "You and the Constitution" [educational material on the Constitution], undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - COSATU (Congress of South African Trade Unions)
    - "Labour Intensive Public Works Projects Can Provide Jobs and Help to Develop Commununities" [manual], undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - NUM News [official newsletter of the National Union of Metalworkers], 1997 March (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "Our Political Economy: Understanding the Problems" [a handbook for COSATU shop stewards], 1992 March (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - The Shopsteward, 1994 Apr/May, 1996 Aug/Sep, 1997 Feb/March (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - "Reading the Financial Pages of a Newspaper: a Guide for Workers," by David Jarvis, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Democratic Party (DP), "The Death of the Rainbow Nation: Unmasking the ANC's Programme of Re-racialisation", undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Environmental Justice Networking Forum
    - Environmental Justice Networker, nos. 8, 12, 1995 / 1996, 1996 / 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Join South Africa's growing movement for environmental justice [flier], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - "Lessons to be Learnt From Visiting Engineers" [unpublished manuscript], undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Episcopal Churchpeople for a Free Southern Africa (ECSA) [bulletin], 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "GroundWork," vol. 5, nos. 4, 5 [Border Rural Committee Newsletter], 1997 Nov, December (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Hendricks, Gertjie Billy, "My Tribute to Princess Diana" [collections of poems], undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Homeless Talk [monthly newspaper, 3 issues], 1996 December / 1997 Jan, 1997 Jun, 2003 February (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Human Rights Commission, Special Report, "Three Years of Destabilisation: A Record of Political Violence in South Africa from July 1990 to June 1993" (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Human Sciences Research Council (HSRC) [media release and research reports on South African issues], 1996 Jun, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Imbizo, no. 2 [research in progress series, published by Community Peace Foundation], 1994 December (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Institute for African Alternatives (IFAA), "Government by the People? Popular Participation in Government Decision-making" [proceedings of workshop organized by IFAA and Reconstruction and Development Programme (RDP), National Office], 1996 February 28, 29 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Institute for Democracy in South Africa (IDSA) [information bulletin and research papers]
    - DSA In Depth: Reconstructing Education, Franklin Sonn, ed., 1994 February (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Public Information Series, nos. 1-4, 1995, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - "The Role of Identity in Building a Common Democratic Culture in South Africa," by Robert B. Mattes [paper delivered at the Mayibuye Centre/Nordic African Institute Conference on "National Identity and Democracy," University of the Wester Cape], 1997 March 14-18 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Institute for Multi-Party Democracy (IMPD) [newsletter and research papers]
    - "IMPD News," vol. 6, no. 1, 1997 February (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Towards Democracy [3 issues and reader survey], 1996- 1997, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Institute for Security Studies, "ISS Papers," nos. 26-29, 1997 November-1998 March (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - International Congress of Vexillology [Program of the XVII Congress held in Cape Town, South Africa], 1997 August 10-15 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - "The Internationalisation of the Afrikaner's Struggle for Self-Determination," Dr. Natie Luyt, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - "The Iron Road to the Sea: Pretoria-Maputo, One Hundred Years," by Eric Conradie [eastern railway centennial publication], 1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - "Juluka," vol. 4, no. 6; vol. 5, no. 2; vol. 8, no. 1[a newsletter for those interested in South Africa], 1995, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Kanti, 1997 May (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Khanya College, "Debating GEAR" (Growth, Employment and Redistribution) [Khanya College economic literacy series], 1997 September (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Land and Rural Digest: the record of rural people's policy, vol. 1, no. 1 [publication of the Environment and Development Agency Trust (EDA), the Rural Development Services Network (RDSN) and the National Land Committee (NLC), 2 copies and fold-out calendar], 1998 Jun/July (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Malikongwa, Jackson K., 1900-1970 [tombstone unveiling ceremony], 1992 August 29 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mayibuye Centre for History and Culture in South Africa, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - National Productivity Institute (NPI), "Productive Affirmative Action Guidelines" [pamphlet], 1997 February (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - National Party (NP) [statement of F. W. De Klerk to the Truth and Reconciliation Committee], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Nene, Phineas Pika [memorial service], 1993 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Nisaa Institute for Women's Development: "Woman Abuse in South Africa: An Exploratory Study," by Zubeda Dangor, Prof. Lee Ann Hoff, Renae Scott, 1996 August (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Pan Africanist Congress
    - PAC Bulletin, vol. 1, no. 3, 1996 June / July (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - "Policy positions on redistribution to promote socioeconomic development" by Sipho Shabalala, 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - "P.E.N. News," no. 196 [publication of the South African P.E.N. Centre, an affiliate of International P.E.N.], 1997 June (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Performing Arts Council Transvaal, 1995 May-July (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - The Prescon Group [flier, South African emigration], 1996 May (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Revolutionary Socialist, nos. 34-36, 1997- 1998 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Robben Island Reunion, Ahmed Kathrada, Nelson Mandela, Mxolisi Mgxashe, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Die Saak vir Afrikaans, J. L. van Schaik, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Saint-Joseph: Des Origines à Nos Jours, Les Cahiers de Notre Histoire, no. 34, 1992 June (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - "Signposts," vol. 12, no. 1A, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - South African Association for Promoting International Cooperation, 1995 August 10, 1997 June (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - South African Broadcasting Corporation (SABC): Radio & TV, no. 5, 1994 July-September (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - South African Communist Party (SACP) [publications], 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - South African Government
    - Auditor-General: "Special Report of the Auditor-General on the Investigation into the Mpumalanga Rural Housing Project", 1997 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Boere-Afrikanerland is Streeksverband, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - The Constitution of the Republic of South Africa, 1996 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - "Democracy, development and peace: a guide through the transitional challenges facing the Western Cape", 1994 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - "The Foundation for a Better Life has been Laid: the Government's Mid-term Report to the Nation", 1997 February (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Land Info, vol. 4, no. 1 [Department of Land Affairs], 1996 Dec/1997 January (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Makumane Biotsekong, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - "Die mense se leiers" [pamphlet], 1995 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Ninth Parliament, Opening speech to the Fifth Session [F. W. de Klerk?], 1993 January 29 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - The Permanent Mission of South Africa to the United Nations [news highlights from the South African media], 1996 May 1-8 (Box 3, Folder 66)